[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers", "Miss White"]}, "docId": "111201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 20, "question": "What makes you so sure that your client is telling the truth?", "question_tokens": ["What", "makes", "you", "so", "sure", "that", "your", "client", "is", "telling", "the", "truth", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 21, "answer": "Well, I have seen no evidence, Piers, no evidence to support the accusations of Miss White.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "have", "seen", "no", "evidence", ",", "Piers", ",", "no", "evidence", "to", "support", "the", "accusations", "of", "Miss", "White", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 51, "question": "Do you know, Mr. Wood -- Mr. Wood, do you know what the -- do you know what Mr. Cain's messages said?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", ",", "Mr.", "Wood", "--", "Mr.", "Wood", ",", "do", "you", "know", "what", "the", "--", "do", "you", "know", "what", "Mr.", "Cain", "'s", "messages", "said", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ":", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "DT", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 52, "answer": "I know a bit -- I know just a few of them.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "know", "a", "bit", "--", "I", "know", "just", "a", "few", "of", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Wood", "Mr. Wood", "Mr. Cain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last several months"], "PERSON": ["Herman Cain"]}, "docId": "111201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP$", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 74, "question": "How has he paid her?", "question_tokens": ["How", "has", "he", "paid", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 75, "answer": "I know that Herman Cain has -- as he has stated publicly, over the last several months on occasion has helped her with her rent.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "know", "that", "Herman", "Cain", "has", "--", "as", "he", "has", "stated", "publicly", ",", "over", "the", "last", "several", "months", "on", "occasion", "has", "helped", "her", "with", "her", "rent", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 91, "question": "Do you know the answers?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "the", "answers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 92, "answer": "Thank you.", "answer_tokens": ["Thank", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "VBP", "VBN", "RP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 183, "question": "And when a candidate has been accused now by five different women of various forms of sexual misconduct, it is slightly stretching credulity to suggest that all of the women are simply fantasies, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["And", "when", "a", "candidate", "has", "been", "accused", "now", "by", "five", "different", "women", "of", "various", "forms", "of", "sexual", "misconduct", ",", "it", "is", "slightly", "stretching", "credulity", "to", "suggest", "that", "all", "of", "the", "women", "are", "simply", "fantasies", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 184, "answer": "We've had two of them that have spoken out publicly.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'ve", "had", "two", "of", "them", "that", "have", "spoken", "out", "publicly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Monday"], "PERSON": ["Mr. Cain"]}, "docId": "111201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 195, "question": "Herman Cain was giving an interview -- well -- OK, effectively, you said that this kind of allegation, because it didn't involve harassment, was a private matter, right?", "question_tokens": ["Herman", "Cain", "was", "giving", "an", "interview", "--", "well", "--", "OK", ",", "effectively", ",", "you", "said", "that", "this", "kind", "of", "allegation", ",", "because", "it", "did", "n't", "involve", "harassment", ",", "was", "a", "private", "matter", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ":", "RB", ":", "NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "NN", ",", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 196, "answer": "I said very clearly that as I understood the nature of this accusation, which I was unaware of at the time because I didn't learn about it as Mr. Cain didn't learn about it until just a few short hours before the broadcast was going to air on Monday.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "said", "very", "clearly", "that", "as", "I", "understood", "the", "nature", "of", "this", "accusation", ",", "which", "I", "was", "unaware", "of", "at", "the", "time", "because", "I", "did", "n't", "learn", "about", "it", "as", "Mr.", "Cain", "did", "n't", "learn", "about", "it", "until", "just", "a", "few", "short", "hours", "before", "the", "broadcast", "was", "going", "to", "air", "on", "Monday", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Herman Cain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Cain"]}, "docId": "111201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "RP", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 241, "question": "-- making the whole thing up, is it?", "question_tokens": ["--", "making", "the", "whole", "thing", "up", ",", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 242, "answer": "I don't know why she decided to go out and give this interview and make these accusations against Mr. Cain.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "why", "she", "decided", "to", "go", "out", "and", "give", "this", "interview", "and", "make", "these", "accusations", "against", "Mr.", "Cain", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Herman Cain"]}, "docId": "111201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 254, "question": "So why should he tell you?", "question_tokens": ["So", "why", "should", "he", "tell", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 255, "answer": "Well, it would be helpful to your client, given there's no evidence he's paid anybody else if you just said yes, Herman Cain pays a lot of women to help them out when they're in times of need.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "would", "be", "helpful", "to", "your", "client", ",", "given", "there", "'s", "no", "evidence", "he", "'s", "paid", "anybody", "else", "if", "you", "just", "said", "yes", ",", "Herman", "Cain", "pays", "a", "lot", "of", "women", "to", "help", "them", "out", "when", "they", "'re", "in", "times", "of", "need", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 258, "question": "That's like, did you beat your wife last night?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "like", ",", "did", "you", "beat", "your", "wife", "last", "night", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 259, "answer": "No, because he said it.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "because", "he", "said", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["last night"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 357, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 358, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Herman Cain"]}, "docId": "111201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 367, "question": "Did you know -- did you know that Herman Cain was making these payments to this woman?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "know", "--", "did", "you", "know", "that", "Herman", "Cain", "was", "making", "these", "payments", "to", "this", "woman", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", ":", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 368, "answer": "I know what Herman Cain has said publicly.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "know", "what", "Herman", "Cain", "has", "said", "publicly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Herman Cain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", ",", "RB", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 387, "question": "How much money has Herman Cain paid this woman?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "money", "has", "Herman", "Cain", "paid", "this", "woman", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 388, "answer": "I can tell you, again, what I know publicly.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "can", "tell", "you", ",", "again", ",", "what", "I", "know", "publicly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Herman Cain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Herman Cain"]}, "docId": "111201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "EX", "IN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 416, "question": "Do you know whether there is any potential issue there in relation to the nature of these payments?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "whether", "there", "is", "any", "potential", "issue", "there", "in", "relation", "to", "the", "nature", "of", "these", "payments", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "EX", "IN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 417, "answer": "I don't believe there's any potential issue there with respect to the payments on the part of Herman Cain.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "believe", "there", "'s", "any", "potential", "issue", "there", "with", "respect", "to", "the", "payments", "on", "the", "part", "of", "Herman", "Cain", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["100 percent"]}, "docId": "111201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "TO", "NN", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "MD", "CC", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 427, "question": "Are you 100 percent certain that she never, ever stayed in a hotel room with Herman Cain or came to meet him in a city where they had dinner together, where there could be a public record?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "100", "percent", "certain", "that", "she", "never", ",", "ever", "stayed", "in", "a", "hotel", "room", "with", "Herman", "Cain", "or", "came", "to", "meet", "him", "in", "a", "city", "where", "they", "had", "dinner", "together", ",", "where", "there", "could", "be", "a", "public", "record", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "CD", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "RB", ",", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RBR", "RB", ",", "WRB", "EX", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 428, "answer": "Are you ever -- have you ever said with respect to someone else, that you're 100 percent certain about something that person may or may not have done.", "answer_tokens": ["Are", "you", "ever", "--", "have", "you", "ever", "said", "with", "respect", "to", "someone", "else", ",", "that", "you", "'re", "100", "percent", "certain", "about", "something", "that", "person", "may", "or", "may", "not", "have", "done", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Herman Cain"], "PERCENT": ["100 percent"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "111201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "RB", "VBD", "RP", "TO", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 474, "question": "When you heard his lawyer there getting very passionate, very heated, clearly trying to draw some kind of line here, being pretty vicious about the media treatment of his client, what did you make of it?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "heard", "his", "lawyer", "there", "getting", "very", "passionate", ",", "very", "heated", ",", "clearly", "trying", "to", "draw", "some", "kind", "of", "line", "here", ",", "being", "pretty", "vicious", "about", "the", "media", "treatment", "of", "his", "client", ",", "what", "did", "you", "make", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "VBN", ",", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", ",", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 475, "answer": "Well, there are a couple of things that really stood out to me, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "there", "are", "a", "couple", "of", "things", "that", "really", "stood", "out", "to", "me", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "WDT", "NNS", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 491, "question": "Or do you think maybe this is going a little bit far?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "do", "you", "think", "maybe", "this", "is", "going", "a", "little", "bit", "far", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "DT", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "RB", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 492, "answer": "Look, one of the things that we know is that more than the laws and policies that politicians make, in terms of impacting our culture, it is how they conduct themselves.", "answer_tokens": ["Look", ",", "one", "of", "the", "things", "that", "we", "know", "is", "that", "more", "than", "the", "laws", "and", "policies", "that", "politicians", "make", ",", "in", "terms", "of", "impacting", "our", "culture", ",", "it", "is", "how", "they", "conduct", "themselves", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 511, "question": "Do you feel now like this is the tipping point?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "now", "like", "this", "is", "the", "tipping", "point", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 512, "answer": "Well, certainly he has suggested that it is.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "certainly", "he", "has", "suggested", "that", "it", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "111201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 524, "question": "What do you think is going to happen over the next few weeks involving this increasingly unpredictable race?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "is", "going", "to", "happen", "over", "the", "next", "few", "weeks", "involving", "this", "increasingly", "unpredictable", "race", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 525, "answer": "I wish I knew, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "wish", "I", "knew", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 553, "question": "So Vegas?", "question_tokens": ["So", "Vegas", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 554, "answer": "It's a perfect fit for us.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "perfect", "fit", "for", "us", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["February 3rd"]}, "docId": "111201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 557, "question": "When is this happening?", "question_tokens": ["When", "is", "this", "happening", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 558, "answer": "It is starting on February 3rd.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "starting", "on", "February", "3rd", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]